Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU) (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The history of the National Maritime Union, 1967-1968 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    Notes: flyer
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Some significant dates in NMU history, 1967-1968 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Highlights of National Maritime Union History, 1967-1968 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: On a true course, 1962; Publication (Box 257, Folder 1)
    Notes: news papers
  - Item 5: This is the NMU; a picture history of the National Maritime Union of America CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Two years--: a record of struggle and achievement of the East Coast seamen, 1939; Publication (Box 257, Folder 1)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The 24 Hour Strike Watch, Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Statement of policy on joint strike action, Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Maritime Strike Policy / National Convention of Maritime Unions, 1946; Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted May 6-11, 1946
  - Item 4: CMU victory report; progressive, fighting solidarity cracks medieval serfdom in the American merchant marine, 1946; Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
    Notes: 2 copies
  - Item 5: CMU looks ahead, 1946; Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
    Author: Alexander Saxton
  - Item 6: CMU and what it means to deck, engine and radio officers, 1946; Publication (Box 257, Folder 2)
- Committee for Maritime Unity (CMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Maritime Unity is the answer, 1963; Publication (Box 257, Folder 3)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Joint membership meeting - National Maritime Union, 1939; Publication (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The membership wins again: a record of recent events in the National Maritime Union, 1937; Publication (Box 257, Folder 4)
    Author: Joseph Curran
    Notes: second copy
  - Item 3: The Story of the Algic case, Publication (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The coming ship subsidy scandal, 1939; Publication (Box 257, Folder 4)
    Author: William L. Standard
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: ACA News, 1944; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 3 (April, 1944)
  - Item 2: Rank & File West Coast Sailor, 1942; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
    Notes: New Series no.1 (April 3, 1942) - headlines - "Blackie Prevost answers Lundeberg"
  - Item 3: "Post War Planning", 1944; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
    Notes: The Journal of Commerce, New York
  - Item 4: "Postwar Planning Now", 1944; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The N. M. U. forges ahead, 1940; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: American merchant marine under Britain's heel: the influence of British financial interests in preventing the development of American shipping, 1941; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Here's a program ! Smash Hitler, vote NMU !, 1942; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Seamen answer Standard Oil's lies, Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The N.M.U. answers Congressman Bradley., 1940; Publication (Box 257, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Peacetime program of the Natl. Maritime Union, 1945; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: What the Nation's leaders say about National Maritime Union, 1944; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Let's go forwardtogether, 1945; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Heroes in Dungarees: the story of the contribution of American Merchant Seamen to the war effort!, 1943; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
    Notes: comic book
  - Item 5: To all ESSO Seamen, 1944; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Lest we forget, 1945; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Statement submitted by Thomas Ray - William L. Standard - Arthur Mandel, 1945; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
    Author: Thomas Ray; William L. Standard; Arthur Mandel
  - Item 8: The Enemy at home!, 1943; Publication (Box 257, Folder 6)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Address by Philip Murray to the eighth national convention, 1951; Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
    Author: Philip Murray
  - Item 2: Pass the Magnuson-Lesinski Bill!, Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: New York Times tells Congress, legalize the Seamen's hiring halls!, Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Seamen's hiring hall, Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The N.M.U. forges ahead; a report on the status of the National maritime union of America, 1940; Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Pork chops and politics, 1943; Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: This is the NMU; a picture history of the National Maritime Union of America CIO., 1954; Publication (Box 257, Folder 7)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: S.I.U. Seamen, Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Sellout on the front waterfront, Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: National Shipping rules (July 1958), Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: newspapers - misc., Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Democracy for all: NMU manual on parliamentary procedure for ship and shore meetings, 1947; Publication (Box 257, Folder 8)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labor spies in the N.M.U., 1939; Publication (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Pelea por la unidad maritime, 1947; Publication (Box 257, Folder 9)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 3: Fight for maritime unity, 1947; Publication (Box 257, Folder 9)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Handbook for saboteurs, 1965; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The time to act is now!, Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Target NMU: there are lessons for today in the battles of the past: an open letter to the membership, 1966; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: On a true course, NMU - 1937-1962, Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: newspaper
  - Item 5: Architecture: Maritime Union builds dream house, 1964; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: news clipping
  - Item 6: We'll keep the 'Savannah' sailing, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Passing the true word, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Curran's NMU, Headquarters vs. the Men at Sea, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Sellout on the waterfront, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Let Seamen's critics face their widows, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The NMU's 'concrete battleship', 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Security for the Mariner on land and sea, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Time is running out, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Let's outlaw floating firetraps, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: An open letter to the SIU, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: The blind men and the elephant, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: It's all yours..., 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Death rides the rivers, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Curran v. Clifford, the NMU takes on the Pentagon and wins a great victory for all Maritime labor, 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: The Cuban Crisis and U.S. Maritime policy..., 1950-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Industrial Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: Dec. 1966
  - Item 22: Dedication Ceremonies: The Joseph Curran Building, 1964; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: 16-May- 64
  - Item 23: National Shipping Rules, 1960; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: Nov. 1960
  - Item 24: NMU Fifteenth National Convention Call, 1969; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
    Notes: Oct. 6, 1969
  - Item 25: Building Fund Progress Report - 1966, Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Our visit to the U.S.S.R.: a report to the membership of the National Maritime Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1959; Publication (Box 258, Folder 1)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Frontiers Below, 1969; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
    Notes: flyer. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Rule and ruin in the NMU, 1968; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
    Notes: article
  - Item 3: collection of fact sheets - National Maritime Union of America, 1968; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Biographical notes on Mel Baristic., 1973; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Job situation in the Merchant Marine, 1969-1970 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Do you want "Hong Kong" wages?, 1969-1970 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: press release, 1970; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1970; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Target is You!: Know the facts..., 1968; Publication (Box 258, Folder 2)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor spies in the N.M.U., 1939; Publication (Box 258, Folder 3)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: NMU Newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    Notes: Negotiations Bulletin no.8
  - Item 2: NMU Newsletter, 1969; Publication (Box 258, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 10, no.3-11
  - Item 3: NMU Newsletter, 1970; Publication (Box 258, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 11, no.1-2
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A handbook on Seamen's Unemployment Insurance, 1947; Publication (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Seamen's unemployment insurance, 1953; Publication (Box 258, Folder 5)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Heart of the union, 1947; Publication (Box 258, Folder 6)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Official ballot - Referendum on constitutional Amendments and National Council Proposals, 1951; Publication (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: National Shipping Rules -, Publication (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: What time is it, America?..., 1944; Publication (Box 258, Folder 7)
- National Maritime Union of America (NMU), Publication (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: To all Seamen on 'Flags of convenience" Ships., 1960; Publication (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: A to-do tripulante de barcos con 'Bandera de Conveniencia", 1960; Publication (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: IMWU Means Job Security for you, 1960; Publication (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: National Association of Masters Mates and Pilots of America, 1918; Publication (Box 258, Folder 8)
- International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots (IOMM&P), Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Main Channel, 1960; Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
    Notes: Unofficial, unauthorized publication for the members of IOMM&P Local no. 90
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1968; Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: History of the Association, its remarkable growth and development, 1922; Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Retirement Plan :Northwest Marine Retirement Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Northwest Marine Welfare Trust, 1959; Publication (Box 258, Folder 9)
- National Association of Masters Mates and Pilots of America, Publication (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Deck officers attend school run by union, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    Notes: news clippings
  - Item 2: Arbitrator asked for wage review, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Ship officers call new issue 'phony', 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: News of interest in shipping world, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Ship union agrees to defer walkout, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Lines still reject pilot hiring hall, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Mediation offered to bar ship strike, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Union makes bid to independents, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: New Parley hopes to avert a strike, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Mates and owners still in deadlock, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Lines still reject pilot hiring hall, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Ship tie-up looms on east and gulf, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Shipping walkout looms on 2 coasts, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Last-minute Federal Parley seeks to avert ship tie-up, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Union will invoke AFL's full weight, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Hiring plan upheld for ship officers, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Deck officers set dispute deadline, 1948-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Wage rise is won by tug crews, 1948-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Ship unions note unemployment rise, 1948-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Two sea unions talk with the US mediators, 1948-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Truce is accepted by masters, mates, 1948-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Mediators fail to sway masters, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: 5 per cent pay increase granted masters, mates and pilots in west, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Deck union, lines trade rejections, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Masters to meet operators today, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Stalemate holds in officer dispute, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: Masters and pilots reopen wage fight, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Pilot talks snag on rotary hiring, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Ship officers set Saturday strike, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Contract is extended, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Ships' officers ask pay rise, hiring hall, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Mediator will study Marine pension plea, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: Kickback for jobs denied by sea union, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: Ship lines to insist on officer selection, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Sea union talks resume, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: Ship officer union resumes parleys, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 37: Mediation stays ship strike here, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: Sea officers set new contract aim, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Ship masters get pact with owners, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: Four ships tied up in Masters' Strike, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: mates, operators talk again today, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 42: 3 Unions accuse operators of ship, 1949-1950 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: Mediator presides at contract talks, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Ship officer union threatens strike, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: Sea union Parleys, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Pact held victory for ship officers, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 47: Ship union maps hiring 'clean up', 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 48: Masters and owners renew strike talks, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 49: Shipping news and notes, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 50: Owners and officers continue job dispute, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 51: Mates strike off, contract reached, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 52: Ship union state welfare fund bid, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 53: Meany set to umpire ship strike, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 54: Ship strike, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 55: Clerk work by Captains denounced, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 56: Deck officers win welfare rise, 1949-1959 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 57: Deck union maps welfare change, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 58: Events of interest in shipping world, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 59: Ship officers don't strike, but dock tie-up continues, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 60: Ferry strike averted, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 61: Deck officer union presents demands, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 62: Mates, operators meet here today, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 63: Negro seamen ask for jobs on ships, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 64: Ferry tie-up threatened, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 65: Seamen to get more near Chinese coast, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 66: Union for joining of Naval Reserve, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 67: Sea union leader spurns Soviet bid, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 68: Wage Parley set for ship masters, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)
  - Item 69: Court acts in ship tie-up, 1948-1954 (Box 258, Folder 10)